want i can solve this problem
gave fifty here old
deu 50 guy
but I don't have
has Cara
has 10 count hand
I thank you Cara
can be
so maybe you can
yesterday was bonzão
the Dog Walker parade
fifty tale walking with dog uncle
but today I won't stay
waiting for the phone to ring but it's not on bro
and I'm going to put my mind out now
and that's it
Oh young man, I wanted a favor
you can only put 1 little bit of detergent for me
you're welcome
thank you saw
soap water and a little connecting with people
soon face let's go
depend on ah
has vacancy
put if you don't have a vacancy you don't work let's go there
put the music there
and
there man
how are you verizão
you who are the owner
yes man
I came to have a look
I saw something in the window
I wanted to ask you
see this here
Everton
the reflection is blurring
cannot view
the product in a way you deserve it
jail passes
can't see what's going on
the sunlight is beating against
works with sales
you don't show your product
suddenly it doesn't sell
and this display case here in this pattern
with me
leave this aesthetic to value your product more
bora accepts pix too
make a
i can't man
with me
I am professional
as much as you want
five minutes
I don't waste time
not dirty
does not fall
water I have all the products here
I am a prepared man
space game together
then my two fifty here old gave a clean
the guy is the entrepreneurial incentive
gratitude
liked the trap or not
na real mano
nobody wants a window cleaner
when you say that the product
of the person is not being well
exposed
messes with the customer's pocket
and then the guy talks
bro maybe if it's a factor i can sell more
this guy is bringing a benefit to my store
so i will close
if you come to a store and talk
ah can i clean the window for you
few people will close
is on
I will solve this problem
these two here i can do it very quickly
use five minutes
have the same material for ten real
and must because of the foggy glass
can be
caraca hand
I'm cleaning the window
that mattress
look I'm looking here at your products
let me ask you
by chance you have resale
the Cocoa Show has resale
after
as you buy more you get other points
I don't mind registering
only you have the minimum first purchase
worth it
oh i think it's worth it
give me 1 chocolate
ah lie you'll give me 1 chocolate
hope this works out there you see
give luck
oh thank you
very cool
thank you very much saw
sympathy
AI caraca
that's it bro let's go up
Why you can't touch this
i feel like you guys
Can't touch this
Break It Down
eita coco my man
thank you heart bro
immense gratitude to you there
thank you from the heart
I here at chevas doing 1 live Ali ó on the neighboring network
and here ó eating bread
salami cheese
and I will show you there
gives a first-hand spoiler
hand-to-hand
how much i did today
is the power to connect with people o
and having money here in the car too
tamo together
You can't touch this